guidetrip.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy | GuideTrip

Public Pages / Privacy policy

1.Introduction 

GuideTrip will always maintain your privacy. GuideTrip gathers certain types of information about you as part of our operations. This [Privacy Policy](http://www.guidetrip.com/privacy-policy) explains the types of information we may gather, and what we do with it when you browse the Website. Capitalized terms in this Privacy Policy have the meanings defined in the [Terms of Use](http://www.guidetrip.com/terms-of-use). 

Back to top

2\. Information used for statistical and related purposes' 

When you use the Site, we collect certain data (including your IP address, browser type and operating system, the number of sites you visit, the duration of your visits, if you are a returning visitor or not, from where you came to the Site, and other similar information). We use this information for statistical purposes, to improve your experience on the Site, to make it easier to use, to better tailor it to your interests and needs, or to speed up your future activities and experience on the Site. We use this information anonymously and in the aggregate. If you transfer additional information to us, for example when you carry out booking queries or fill data into forms, we may evaluate such information anonymously and in the aggregate for statistical purposes, even without prior registration and even if no booking takes place. 

Back to top

3\. Personal Information 

Personal information is collected when you voluntarily purchase GuideTrip's services or register as a traveler. Personal information may include e-mail address, passwords, telephone numbers, address and other information & data needed to provide our services to you. We only require minimum personal information and use this information only to provide our services as requested by you.' All information submitted to us is restricted in our offices. Employees who need the information for safety purpose are granted access to personal information, including, but not limited to messages, experiences and other information. We DO NOT transfer your Personal Information to GuideTrip's third-party service providers. We DO NOT share, sell or distribute your Personal Information with unrelated third parties, except under these limited circumstances: 

Back to top

4.Internal Messages Through GuideTrip's System 

GuideTrip provides a method for communicating with Local Experts on our system. We monitor all messages with the intention of ensuring that your Local Expert is helping you and to ensure compliance with the Terms of Use of GuideTrip. 

Back to top

5\. Aggregate Information 

We may collect aggregate information about overall user's activities online such as the number of unique travellers, Local Experts pages accessed most frequently or the search terms entered. This information may be tracked through your Internet Protocol (IP) address, a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. When you request a page from our site, your IP address may be logged. We may also collect aggregate information through the use of a cookie, which is a small data file that Web sites store on your hard drive when you visit them. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies however you may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter certain identifying information to gain access to certain parts of the Website. We use aggregate information to improve your user experience by determining which areas and features are most popular and which may need to be improved. GuideTrip does not use IP addresses or cookies to retrieve any information from your computer. 

Back to top

6\. Third Party Data Sharing 

GuideTrip does not share personal information with third parties unless required to by a lawful request such as a supoenae or if we believe that the health or safety of another person or the general public may be compromised if we do not. Aggregate information for GuideTrip is collected by internally and we confirm that no personally identified information is distributed by us. 

Back to top

7\. Links to Third Parties 

This site may contain links to sites other than our own and those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as GuideTrip. If you visit other sites by clicking on a link from our site, you should determine their privacy policies before using their information or services. 

Back to top

8\. Leaving GuideTrip 

You can choose to remove your email address from our database at any time. Please drop us an email at [info@guidetrip.com](mailto:info@guidetrip.com?Subject=Question%20for%20the%20GuideTrip%20team) to do so. 

Back to top

9\. Updation and Correction of Information 

GuideTrip provides you with the ability to change and modify information previously provided. Please follow the appropriate link when you log into your account. 

Back to top

10\. Additional Information 

No one can guarantee that transmission of data over the Internet is completely secure. It may be possible for third parties to unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communication. While we strive to protect your personal information, GuideTrip cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and we shall not be liable for any special, incidental or consequential damages you may suffer in the event that your transmission of data was intercepted. 

Back to top

**GuideTrip reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such changes will be posted online. Please visit this page regularly to keep yourself updated on any changes or modifications as made by us. Please contact us via e-mail at[info@guidetrip.com](mailto:info@guidetrip.com?Subject=Question%20for%20the%20GuideTrip%20team) if you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy. ******
